<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
	<author>NX Modding</author>
	<version>1.0.0.0</version>
	<title>
		<en>Bi-Directional Pallets</en>
		<de>Bi-Direktionale Paletten</de>
		<fr>Palettes Bi-Directionnelles</fr>
		<ru>Двунаправленные Поддоны</ru>
	</title>
	<description>
<en><![CDATA[Bi-Directional Pallets turns every refillable tool (seeders, sprayers, trailers) into a two-way pallet hub. Empty into a tool from a stack of pallets, OR pour leftover product back into empty pallets and big-bags so nothing is wasted.

Features:
- Pull-fill: chain-load a tool from any number of pallets / big-bags with a single command
- Push-fill: top up nearby empty/partial pallets straight from your tank
- Per-tool toggles for both directions, persisted with the savegame
- On-screen overlay shows fill levels and selection order
- Manual selection lets you pick which item to start the chain from
- Multiplayer aware - all transfers are server-authoritative
]]></en>
<de><![CDATA[Bi-Direktionale Paletten macht aus jedem nachfüllbaren Werkzeug (Sämaschinen, Spritzen, Anhänger) einen Zwei-Wege-Palettenknoten. Leere mehrere Paletten in ein Gerät - oder gieße Reste zurück in leere Paletten und Big-Bags.

Funktionen:
- Pull-Fill: Mehrere Paletten / Big-Bags mit einem Befehl in das Gerät kettenladen
- Push-Fill: Nachfüllen umliegender leerer Paletten direkt aus dem Tank
- Pro-Gerät Schalter für beide Richtungen, im Spielstand gespeichert
- Bildschirm-Anzeige der Füllstände und Reihenfolge
- Manuelle Auswahl des Startobjekts der Kette
- Mehrspieler-fähig - alle Transfers serverseitig
]]></de>
<fr><![CDATA[Palettes Bi-Directionnelles transforme chaque outil rechargeable (semoirs, pulvérisateurs, remorques) en hub de palettes bidirectionnel. Videz plusieurs palettes dans l'outil OU reversez le produit restant dans des palettes vides.

Caractéristiques:
- Pull-Fill: chaîner le remplissage depuis plusieurs palettes / big-bags via une seule commande
- Push-Fill: remplir des palettes vides / partielles à proximité depuis le réservoir
- Bascules par outil pour les deux sens, sauvegardées avec la partie
- Affichage des niveaux et de l'ordre de sélection
- Sélection manuelle du premier élément de la chaîne
- Compatible multijoueur - transferts côté serveur
]]></fr>
<ru><![CDATA[Двунаправленные Поддоны превращают любой инструмент с заправкой в двусторонний узел. Заправляйтесь сразу с нескольких поддонов ИЛИ сливайте остатки обратно в пустые поддоны и биг-бэги.

Возможности:
- Pull-Fill: цепная заправка с нескольких поддонов одной командой
- Push-Fill: дозаправка соседних поддонов прямо из бака
- Переключатели для каждого направления, сохраняются в игре
- Экранная индикация уровней и порядка
- Ручной выбор первого элемента цепи
- Сетевой режим - все транзакции на сервере
]]></ru>
	</description>

	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<iconFilename>icon_BiDirectionalPallets.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="register.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="core/BiDirSettings.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="language/l10n" />

	<actions>
		<action name="BIDIR_TOGGLE_PULL" category="VEHICLE"/>
		<action name="BIDIR_TOGGLE_PUSH" category="VEHICLE"/>
		<action name="BIDIR_CYCLE_PICK"  category="VEHICLE"/>
	</actions>
</modDesc>
